<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BlockRocket Engineering | Helping you understanding Blockchain | BlockRocket.tech on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BlockRocket Engineering | Helping you understanding Blockchain | BlockRocket.tech on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a functioning arts DAO</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/building-a-functioning-arts-dao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/building-a-functioning-arts-dao/</guid>
      <description>Our take on the components required to build a profit seeking DAO that curates and sells NFTs
After our recent launch of the experimental DAO, Osaka DAO, it soon became apparent that even with all the current DAO hype, there still isn’t the right sort of DAO aimed at creative curation and revenue generation that aspires to be profit seeking. Although it is in the name most current implementations are not very autonomous!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAOSaka: The facts and figures</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/daosaka-the-facts-and-figures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/daosaka-the-facts-and-figures/</guid>
      <description>From funding the DAO, to commissioning the art, selling the digital assets, and returning a shareholder profit! 😍
After Berlin Blockchain week we had seen the power of community through DAOs (Decentralised Autonomous Organisations) with the MetaCartel demo day and DAO. Read more about their efforts to promote dApps here.
The MetaCartel! (can you spot us in the picture 👀)
After we got back to Manchester and arranged a call with Peter ‘pet3rpan’ to discuss an experiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ERC721 Secondary Sale Commission Conundrum 😐</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/the-erc721-secondary-sale-commission-conundrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/the-erc721-secondary-sale-commission-conundrum/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR it’s complicated!
At BlockRocket we build dApps and a fair few of them use non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that follow the ERC721 standard. Once the digital assets are live on the blockchain they can commonly be re-sold on secondary markets (primary being the original sale and minting of the token).
The majority of NFTs currently being traded on marketplaces use transfer functions that do not have any *value *exchange bar the token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brave new world: blockchain and the emergence of Web 3.0 | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/a-brave-new-world-blockchain-and-the-emergence-of-web-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/a-brave-new-world-blockchain-and-the-emergence-of-web-3/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain — and its associated technologies — is set to play a key role in the evolution of Web 3.0, and the democratic decentralisation of data.
Web 1.0 — The beginning Back in the 90s when the internet became a living breathing beast, we saw the birth of a new paradigm, a revolution in the form of information and communications. Suddenly the world didn’t seem like such a big place; people could communicate, share ideas and exchange data, and applications could be built which could be accessed by billions of people around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlockRocket visits Parliament | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/blockrocket-visits-parliament-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/blockrocket-visits-parliament-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>All Party-Parliamentary Group on Blockchain Summer Reception
After attending and participating in several APPG evidence meetings with a shared goal at governmental level to advance blockchain technology adoption we got an invite to Summer Reception by the chair of group Damien Moore MP.
So we boarded the train south as we love good chat with likeminded individuals plus there was a promise of the odd beer too 🍻
A CryptoKaiju came along for the ride!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Ethereum | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/scaling-ethereum-what-scaling-solutions-can-you-use-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/scaling-ethereum-what-scaling-solutions-can-you-use-today/</guid>
      <description>How projects can leverage the latest scaling technologies to build highly scalable Ethereum applications
credits to district0x — https://education.district0x.io/general-topics/
At BlockRocket we are often asked by clients, how can they can leverage public blockchains like Ethereum without suffering from known blockers such as scalability and transactions costs.
Today, the Ethereum ecosystem is maturing and scaling solutions, also known as layer 2 solutions (L2), are becoming production ready. We have been building with a variety of tools and frameworks that now allows us to advise our clients on the best approach right now on what can be realistically done and where we see this technology going.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>