<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BlockRocket Blog | Blockchain at the coalface | BlockRocket.tech on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BlockRocket Blog | Blockchain at the coalface | BlockRocket.tech on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A brave new world: blockchain and the emergence of Web 3.0 | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/a-brave-new-world-blockchain-and-the-emergence-of-web-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/a-brave-new-world-blockchain-and-the-emergence-of-web-3/</guid>
      <description>A brave new world: blockchain and the emergence of Web 3.0 Blockchain — and its associated technologies — is set to play a key role in the evolution of Web 3.0, and the democratic decentralisation of data.
Web 1.0 — The beginning Back in the 90s when the internet became a living breathing beast, we saw the birth of a new paradigm, a revolution in the form of information and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlockRocket visits Parliament | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/blockrocket-visits-parliament-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/blockrocket-visits-parliament-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>BlockRocket visits Parliament #blockchain All Party-Parliamentary Group on Blockchain Summer Reception
After attending and participating in several APPG evidence meetings with a shared goal at governmental level to advance blockchain technology adoption we got an invite to Summer Reception by the chair of group Damien Moore MP.
So we boarded the train south as we love good chat with likeminded individuals plus there was a promise of the odd beer too 🍻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Ethereum — what scaling solutions can you use today? | Blog | BlockRocket.tech</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/scaling-ethereum-what-scaling-solutions-can-you-use-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/scaling-ethereum-what-scaling-solutions-can-you-use-today/</guid>
      <description>Scaling Ethereum — what scaling solutions can you use today? How projects can leverage the latest scaling technologies to build highly scalable Ethereum applications
credits to district0x — https://education.district0x.io/general-topics/
At BlockRocket we are often asked by clients, how can they can leverage public blockchains like Ethereum without suffering from known blockers such as scalability and transactions costs.
Today, the Ethereum ecosystem is maturing and scaling solutions, also known as layer 2 solutions (L2), are becoming production ready.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>